afw.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy | AFW.com

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for https://www.afw.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

## Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us. When you create an account to use our site, we ask for information such as your name and email address. This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required. This information is helpful to us in understanding who our customers are so that we can improve our products and services. When you sign up for our notification services, we require your email address to send you the requested information. When you use our site to tells us what you think, we may ask for your email address but will never display it on the site.

When you place an order, we ask for information that we need to process your order: your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and your credit card number and its expiration date. We use this information for billing purposes, to fill your order and update you about its status. If we have trouble processing your order, we'll use this information to contact you. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. Please be aware that we work with third parties for shipping and fulfilling some orders, and that we will need to provide the requisite information with our suppliers and shipping companies. If your information has been provided to a third party vendor for fulfillment (for example, a direct ship or parcel ship order), that company may retain your information and that information will be governed by their site policies. Also note that we may share some general statistics (like most active age group), sales, traffic patterns, and related site information with reputable third parties. These statistics will not include any personal or identifying information.

Finally, AFW may disclose information in special cases if we believe that such information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the terms of our website or the rights of others. We may also disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, and for administrative purposes necessary to maintain, service and improve our products and services.

### Automatically Collected Information.

We may automatically collect certain types of non-personally identifiable information when your visit or use our site, including your IP address, browser information, operating system information, device information, and the date, time, length of stay, and specific pages accessed during your visit to our site.

## User Generated Content

As between you and Us, you are the owner of all the photos, videos, music, sounds, comments, profile information or other content you share with American Furniture Warehouse and its affiliates or that you post, share, or tag to other websites or apps (collectively “User Content”).

You give American Furniture Warehouse and its affiliates permission to use your User Content in the form of a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, fully paid up, worldwide license in perpetuity to use, reproduce, display, perform, distribute, create derivative works from and otherwise use your User Content in connection with AFW.com (the “Site”) and for other American Furniture Warehouse marketing purposes. For example, but not by way of limitation, American Furniture Warehouse may use your User Content in advertisements, product descriptions, customer communications, or other marketing materials. This means your User Content may be visible, sent to, and viewed by all other users of the Site or on other webpages or apps, in emails or in other marketing materials. The permission you give Us does not prevent you from using the User Content for your own purposes or letting others use your User Content for their purposes. Also, the permission you give Us means American Furniture Warehouse does not owe you anything else in connection with American Furniture Warehouse’s use of the User Content.

Furthermore, you promise to American Furniture Warehouse that you own or have permission to your User Content, have paid any fees related to your use of the User Content, and that any of your User Content does not violate the intellectual property rights of any third party including: copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret, publicity or privacy rights, or any other proprietary right. In addition, American Furniture Warehouse may refuse to accept or transmit User Content for any reason. We may also remove User Content at any time and for any reason.

## Analytics

We use Google Analytics to monitor traffic patterns on our web site so we may improve the site's content and organization. Google Analytics is Google's analytics tool that helps AFW understand how their visitors engage with our properties. It may use a set of cookies to collect information and report website usage statistics without personally identifying individual visitors to Google.

## Cookies

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be 100% guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your information, AFW cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

## Browser Recommendations

For enhanced security, we recommend using a modern web browser like Chrome, Firefox, Safari or Microsoft ® Internet Explorer version 9.0 or higher, all of which enable SSL. We also recommend setting your browser's preferences to accept cookies and enable JavaScript.

## Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-800-992-7997 or via email at service@afwonline.com.
